gundamkitscollection.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy - Gundam Kits Collection News and Reviews

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Gundam Kits Collection News and Reviews collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [//www.gundamkitscollection.com/](https://www.gundamkitscollection.com/) website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Gundam Kits Collection News and Reviews.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.  
  
**Push notifications**  
**  
** Gundam Kits Collection News and Reviews have added a push notification app effective May 8, 2016. This program is 100% safe and will not collect personal identifications from the readers subscribed to it. Readers can receive news from our website even if they are not on any of our social media websites like Facebook, Twitter or Pinterest. 

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Gundam Kits Collection News and Reviews may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To improve our Site_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to users by advertising partners; Hobby Link Japan, Big Bad Toy Store, NewTypeHQ and Omocha Japan, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.  
  
**Commenting**

As of April 2017, Gundam Kits Collection require readers to use their Google accounts to comment on our website's posts. Each comments will be reviewed by our comment moderator for our reader's protection from profanity and abusers. Spam comments will be automatically deleted.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Gundam Kits Collection News and Reviews has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
<https://www.gundamkitscollection.com/>  
[[email protected]](https://www.gundamkitscollection.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

This document was last updated on February 28, 2019  
<https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/gundamkitscollection.com>
